养老院
刚才真是爽翻了 宝贝儿
Whoo! That was good, baby.
我敢说从你上次中风后就再没有过刚那销魂的高潮表情
I bet you ain't made a face like that since your last stroke.
别点火 我吸着氧...
Don't light that. I'm on oxygen...
恭喜你 Denzel
Congratulations, Denzel.
这是你本月第四次因性事牵连而受伤
This is your fourth sex-related injury this month.
我能说个啥 医生? 和老女人睡觉很危险的
What can I say, doc? Sleeping with old ladies is dangerous.
救护车
我去
Oh, shit!
不是让你用牙"咬"
Ah! Teefers! Teefers!
Denzel 你对老年妇女的反常迷恋
Denzel, your unnatural attraction to elderly women
在医学上称作恋老癖 这种病通常是致命的
is a condition called gerontophilia, and it is often fatal.
致命? 我可以为老年穴去谋杀 但可不想被谋杀
Fatal? I'll kill for pussy, but I ain't gonna die for it.
幸运的是 这种病可以通过一种简单的门诊手术被治愈
Luckily, this condition can be cured by a simple outpatient procedure.
- 真的? 好 那就做吧 - 先来做点准备工作
- Really? Okay, let's do it. - Let's get you prepped.
嘿 你在我脑瓢儿干啥...
Hey, what are you doing back...
来做测试看看
And now for the test.
Tammy Gladys 请你们进来一下好吗?
Tammy! Gladys! Could you come in here, please?
好了 Denzel 你对哪位比较有性趣?
Now, Denzel, which do you prefer?
俏护士? 还是死老妪?
Nurse? Or hearse?
我正式宣布你已经被治愈 Denzel 感觉怎么样?
I now pronounce you cured, Denzel. How do you feel?
我想当一名消防员
I wanna be a fireman!
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
脆莓公园
♢ 症 ♢ 偏执绝非过错
♢ 井脑湿 ♢ 旗木
联合译制 ❤
我不仅治好了恋老癖
And not only am I cured of my lust for grannies,
还泡上了Kuzniak医生的俏护士Tammy
I'm dating Dr. Kuzniak's hot nurse, Tammy.
那可真是好 伙计
That's great, buddy.
是啊 我还一直以为你是什么怪胎呢
Yeah. I was starting to think you were some kind of weirdo.
吃香包的剃光毛大猩猩还好意思说这话
And that's coming from a shaved gorilla who eats potpourri.
吃香包让我的屁闻起来像圣诞大餐
It makes my farts smell like Christmas.
- 我也有事要宣布 - 得癌症了 得癌症了 得癌症了
- I have big news, too. - Cancer, cancer, cancer...
不是哦 我也正和人拍拖着呢
No. I'm also dating someone.
她叫TJ
Her name is TJ.
简直热辣得烫人 还很擅长运动呢
She's smoking hot. She's athletic.
Steve 你是不能和在游戏中创建的角色约会的
Steve, uh, you can't date the characters you create on Wii Fit.
你废话太多了
Oh, leave Steve alone.
能和想象出来的女朋友谈恋爱也是件甜蜜的事呢
I think it's sweet he's got an imaginary girlfriend.
她不是想象出来的 我会证明给你看
She's not imaginary. And I'll prove it.
我们来四人约会吧
Let's go on a double date.
没问题 我带上Tammy 你就带上你的二次元Kate
All right. I'll bring Tammy. You bring Kate made-up-ton.
早上好 同事们
Bonjour, mon co-travailleurs.
法语
你们不想知道我为什么说法语吗?
Don't you want to know why I'm speaking French?
- 因为你是个婊子 - 错
- Because you're a whore. - No.
我要去参加国家公园小姐选美大赛了
I'm entering the Miss national park beauty pageant.
我还真是欲尿 (预料) 不出
I couldn't give two squirts of piss.
认真的 我前列腺有梅丽莎·麦卡西的头那么大
Seriously, I got a prostate the size of Melissa McCarthy's head.
美国女演员
冠军会获得一张往返于世界任何地方的机票
First place is a round-trip ticket to anywhere in the world,
而我要去巴黎
and I'm going to Paris.
这么确定第一名非你莫属?
How can you be so sure you'll win?
拜托 再确定不过了好吧
Please. It's the surest bet ever.
我的对手们一看都是...
The rest of the contestants look like...
- 林警样 - 有必要么 Ethel?
- park rangers. - Really, Ethel?
选美是一件充满了男性至上主义的的蠢事
Beauty pageants are stupid and sexist.
拥有林警身材的人都是这么认为的
That's what people who look like park rangers always say.
"你死定了 死胖子"
"You're a dead man, fatso."
说你呢 Connie
Oh, Connie, it's for you.
"我说的是你 Woody Johnson"
"I'm talking about you, Woody Johnson."
别特么再砸老子的窗户了
Stop breaking my [Bleep] window!
Woody 为什么说"你死定了"?
Woody, why did that rock say you're a dead man?
没什么
Oh, it's nothing.
也许是公园里的动物们和咱逗着玩呢
Probably just some of the animals having fun.
Steve 戴上这假胡子去发动我的车
Steve! Put on this mustache and go start my car.
- 不要 - 抓住你了 Johnson
- No! - I got you now, Johnson!
大爷的 我还以为别处再不安全 暗黑死胡同也是安全的
God damn it. I thought the one place I'd be safe is a dark, dead-end alley.
闭上你的狗嘴
Shut the hell up!
快把欠我的两万刀还给我
Now give me the 20 grand you owe me.
我必须不能再赌魁地奇了
I have gotta stop betting on Quidditch.
《哈利·波特》系列中重要的空中团队对抗运动
还以为赫奇帕奇学院赢定了呢
I thought Hufflepuff was due.
《哈利·波特》系列中霍格沃茨魔法学校的四大学院之一
你最好立刻还钱 否则我会找来个玻璃棒
You better pay up now. Or I'm gonna take a glass rod,
用喷灯把它加热加烫 接着插入你的...
heat it up with a blowtorch, and stick it up your...
肿么啦 宝贝儿 Scoodles在毯毯上尿尿啦?
Hi, baby. Oh, Scoodles went pee pee on the rug?
爸比马上就回家家帮你清理干净哦
Well, I'll come home and clean it up straight away.
爸比爱你胜彩虹哟 拜拜
I love you more than rainbows. Buh-bye.
接刚才说的...
So anyway...
玻璃棒 烫死人的玻璃棒
Glass rod... blowtorch...
一阵见血直接插入你的...
and it's going straight up your...
肿么啦 甜果果
Hi, plum fairy.
想吃芝士蛋糕工厂的香滑榛子松露是吧?
Oh, you want hazelnut truffles from the cheesecake factory?
马上买回去 绒绒小喵喵
Well, sure thing, fluffy kitten.
- 刚说哪儿了? - 玻璃棒?
- Where was I? - Glass rod?
没错 谢了 玻璃棒
Right. Thank you. Glass rod!
- 我要... - 等等 再给我个机会
- I'm gonna... - Hold on. Give me another chance.
- 再赌一次 输了双倍给你 - 赌什么?
- A bet. Double or nothing. - On what?
等等 让我想想
Uh, hold on. Let me think.
再确定不过了好吧
It's the surest bet ever.
赌Ethel能赢国家公园小姐选美大赛第一名
On Ethel Anderson winning the Miss national park beauty pageant.
好 就这么说定了
Okay, you're on.
可要是你输了
And when you lose...
我就会用刚才讲到的玻璃棒插入...
I'm gonna take that aforementioned glass rod and...
肿么啦 小绵羊 放了Woody Johnson?
Hey, little lamb. Heh... leave Woody Johnson alone?
- 为啥捏? - 因为他是个好人
- Why? - Because he's a nice man.
她说什么了?
Well, what'd she say?
- 哈 你个吮屌衰人 - 我是吮屌衰人?
- Ha! You are suck penis. - I am suck penis?
- 你最爱吸吮基佬的巨屌
- Hmm. - You are suck big gay penis.
闭嘴 你大爷的 我正努力集中注意力呢
Shut up, God damn it. I'm trying to concentrate.
你输了 轮到我用蛋蛋蹂躏你的脸了
You lose! Now I make sex in your face with my penis balls.
停止
Stop it.
说正经的呢 停下来
I mean it! Cut it out!
人死茶凉
Tea bag termination.
我会报仇的 你个贱种
I'll get you for this, you son of a bitch.
我在大天朝呢 你能把我咋地 傻X?
I in China. What you gonna do, bag of douche?
Woody 清洁工又把壁画给砸坏啦
Woody! The cleaning lady broke another picture.
我想你又会说不是你干的 对吧 Inez?
So, I guess you didn't do that, either, did you, Inez?
就像你说没在我睡觉时打我...
Just like you didn't maul me in my sleep
没买过这些硬派色情熊电影一样?
or order all this hardcore bear porn?
♪ 云雀云雀 可爱的云雀 ♪
♪ Alouette, gentille aloutte ♪
法国儿歌《云雀》
♪ 云雀云雀 来给你梳毛 ♪
♪ aloutte, je te plumarai ♪
你好啊 史上最美林警
Well, hello there, prettiest ranger ever.
你最喜欢哪件裙子?
Which dress do you like best?
我以为你戒掉异装癖了呢
Oh, see, I thought you stopped cross-dressing.
不是给我穿的 你个愚蠢但... 通情达理的妹子
They're not for me, you stupid but ... perceptive lady.
是给你穿的
They're for you.
我会帮你赢得国家公园小姐 从现在起我是你的教练
I'm gonna help you win Miss national park. I'm your new coach.
你开始关心起选美了?
So now you care about the pageant?
当然了 我小命都靠这事来保住了
Hell yeah. My life is on the line here.
我是说 你去巴黎的旅行 我真的很在乎噢
I mean, heh, your trip to Paris. Which I really give a shit about.
少绕弯子 到底什么鬼把戏?
Cut the crap. What's going on?
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
说实话 我从杀人狂McGill那儿借了点钱
The truth is I borrowed some money from manslaughter McGill,
如果你不能在选美上胜出
and if you don't win that pageant,
他会拿一根玻璃棒插入我的...
he's gonna stick a glass rod up my...
好吧 他没说是哪
well, he never told me.
但不管玻璃棒插哪 对我都不是好事啊
But there isn't any good place to stick a glass rod!
我都等不及看到妹子们进来了
I can't wait for the girls to get here.
还从没玩过四人约会呢
I've never been on a double date.
赌20刀 我的妞绝对比你的惹火
20 bucks says my girl's hotter than yours.
- 这我赌定了 - 好啊 帅哥们
- You are so on. - Hey, boys.
- 好啊 宝贝 - 好啊
- Hey, baby. - Hey there.
你的妞呢
Where's your girl?
- 就在这儿 她叫TJ - 不对 她叫Tammy
- Right here. This is TJ. - No this isn't. This is Tammy.
我叫Tammy Jane 我把你俩都约了
It's Tammy Jane. I go by either.
- 没想到吧 - 什么?
- Surprise. - What?
- 你知道这什么意思 对吧? - 懂的 她是个克隆人
- You know what this means, right? - Yeah. She's a clone!
杀了她
Kill her!
不 她要脚踩两条船
No! She's going out with both of us.
这样可不行 你只能选一个
This ain't gonna fly. You gotta choose.
你到底想和谁在一起?
Which one of us do you want?
- 好吧 我选Denzel - 闭嘴 Steve
- Okay. I'm choosing Denzel. - Shut up, Steve.
我宁愿和你 也不要和这天杀的克隆人在一起
Well, I'd rather be with you than a stupid clone.
我可不是克隆人 也不会从你俩中选的
I'm not a clone. And I don't want to choose.
你们俩我都喜欢 不如我们来一场激情三角恋吧?
I like you both. What do you think about a menage a trois?
激情三角恋?
Menage a trois?
为什么要把Denzel的堂兄给扯进来?
What does Denzel's cousin have to do with this?
别犯傻了 Steve
Aw, don't be a dumbass, Steve.
那是一道鸡肉做的菜 对吧?
That's some kind of chicken dish, right?
男生们 我是在和你们说三人同床
Guys, what I'm proposing is a threesome.
那又是什么?
What's that?
Ethel 我都不敢相信你要参加选美比赛
Ethel, I can't believe you're going through with this.
- 选美毁一生啊 - 你咋这么反感选美?
- Pageants ruin people's lives. - Why are you so anti-pageant?
- 你对选美又了解什么? - 只有你猜不到
What do you even know about them? More than you think.
还是个小孩时 我可是世界级的选美冠军
When I was younger, I was a world champion pageant queen.
记住一点 宝贝
Just remember, sweetie.
你又漂亮又有天赋 但如果你输了
You're beautiful and talented, but if you lose,
耶稣会杀了奶奶 送她下地狱
Jesus will kill grandma and send her to hell.
好的 妈妈
Okay, mommy.
差点忘了 你还要喷笑脸棒
Oh, wait. You forgot your energy snort.
还有减肥桶
Time for the skinny bucket.
♪ 美国佬儿去镇上 ♪
♪ Oh, yankee doodle went to town ♪
♪ 骑着一匹小马... ♪
♪ riding on a pony... ♪
但就在要拿到高分的那一刻 我的青春期也到了
But just as I hit my high note, I also hit puberty.
♪ 他在帽子上插根鸡毛 ♪
♪ He stuck a feather in his hat ♪
♪ 取名叫做... ♪
♪ and called it... ♪
♪ 花花公子 ♪
♪ macaroni ♪
我胜出了吗?
Did I win?
那天我不得不走回家
I had to walk home that day.
等我回到家 家里人也都搬走了
And when I got there, my family had moved.
感觉不会再爱了
I never felt loved again.
我告诉你 Ethel 选美大赛本身就很险恶
I'm telling you, Ethel. Pageants are evil.
听起来你只是嫉妒我 因为你不可能再赢比赛了
Sounds like you're just jealous because you can never win one again.
只要我想参加 还是能赢的
I could still win if I wanted to.
赢什么 吃馅饼大赛? 赛狗? 后背痤疮赛?
Win what, a pie-eating contest? A dog show? Most bacne?
最胖影子赛? 最深阴道赛?
Biggest shadow? World's sweatiest cunt?
你走着瞧吧
I'll show you.
我会参加国家公园小姐选美大赛
I'm gonna enter the Miss national park pageant
把你皮包骨的屁股打得落花流水
and beat your skinny little ass!
怎么了? Connie 别和选手吵架
What's going on? Connie! Don't speak to the talent.
事实上 Connie准备参加选美大赛
Actually, Connie has decided to enter the pageant.
想法不错 Connie
Good idea, Connie.
Ethel站在顶着红毛的冰箱旁边 美丽就更能衬托出来了
Ethel will look even prettier standing next to a red-headed refrigerator.
不 我要赢
No, I can win.
赢什么 吃馅饼大赛?
Win what, a pie-eating contest?
那梗我说过了
I already did that one.
- 那最深阴道赛呢? - 也说过了
- How about sweatiest gunt? - Yep.
我靠 Malloy
Goddamn Malloy.
他把这些侮辱纸条给所有人卖了个遍
He's selling these insults to everybody.
得了吧 哥们 我才不乐意三人同床呢
Forget it, man. I ain't doing this threesome.
休想让我和别的男人睡一张床
There ain't no way I'm getting in bed with another dude.
这何止是和别的男人同床 你是和我同床呢
It's not just another dude. You'd be in bed with me.
嘘 Steve 我的屌都听得到
Shh. Steve, my dick can hear you.
拜托 哥们 这事绝对有趣
Come on, man. It'll be fun.
- 你的屌听到了吗? - Steve 我和你说
- Did your dick hear that? - Steve, I'm telling you.
两个大男人玩三人同床危险得很
Two-dude threesomes are dangerous.
- 你说什么? - 我认得一个叫Artie的哥们
- What are you talking about? - I know this guy Artie, right?
他就是玩的两男三人同床 然后不知怎的...
He was doing a two-dude threesome, and then out of nowhere...
胸前被跑漏的精液射了个中
Gets hit in the chest with some runaway jizz.
这玩意一旦遭中可就没得救了
That's some shit you ain't coming back from.
- 天哪... - 你这就觉得可怕了?
- Man... - Oh, you think that's bad?
我哥们Reggie? 和他哥Tyreke也来了个三人同床
My boy Reggie? He and his brother, Tyreke, did a threesome.
结果出了意外...
Shit went wrong...
现在这俩逗逼结婚了
those two motherfuckers is married now.
你看? 大团圆嘛
See? A happy ending.
来嘛 这事一生只有一次的
Come on... this is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
- 拜托? - 好啦好啦
- Please? - Oh, all right.
但咱们要做这事 就得做得尽善尽美
But if we do this thing, we gonna do it right.
该给你上上课了
Time to take you to school.
噢 我必须和学校保持50英尺的距离
Oh, I'm not allowed within 50 feet of those.
我的假释官说 那是"诱惑之屋"
My parole officer calls them "temptation houses."
起步 二 三 四
Step, two, three, four.
转个圈 撅腚露后门
Turn around and show the back door.
现在用你屁股做一遍
Now do it with your ass.
Woody 你在搞什么鬼? 我只有90磅重
Woody, what are you doing? I'm 90 pounds.
没错 奥普拉 我们得把你减到80磅
That's right, Oprah. We need to get you into the 80s.
美国名脱口秀主持人 体型丰满
给我把你的肥屁股晃起来 然后做个金手指
Now shake that fat ass and give me sparkle fingers!
做不出金手指 我就把你的手指头给剪掉
You better make those fingers sparkle or I'll cut 'em off.
- 我了个天呐 Woody - 是我不对 是我不对 很抱歉
- Jesus Christ, Woody! - You're right. You're right. I'm sorry.
给你... 我给你准备了点致胜的小玩意
Here... I got you a little something to help you win.
噢 Woody...
Oh, Woody...
- 等等 这些号码是干嘛的? - 是评委旅馆的房间号码
- Wait, what are these numbers? - It's the judges' hotel rooms.
你得让他们每个人都对你用金手指
You're gonna get sparkle fingered by every single one of them.
萌萌的小Connie去哪儿了?
Oh, where did you go, little cute Connie?
- 我不可能赢的 - 你肯定能赢
- I'll never win. - Of course you can win.
我知道 赢吃派比赛
I know. A pie-eating contest.
1994年度小小可人儿
鲸拉松 "性致"破坏大赛什么的
A whale-a-thon. A boner-killing contest.
错 我说的是选美
No. The pageant.
能不能顺便把"性致"破坏大赛这梗让给我?
And is it cool if I have that boner contest line?
绝对没希望的
This is hopeless.
胡说 我可以帮你赢
Nonsense. I can help you win this thing.
有一个条件 头等奖机票归我
On one condition. I get the first-prize plane ticket.
我要去中国转一圈 顺便宰个熊孩子
My goal is to see China. And murder a child.
为啥不就近在这儿宰一个?
Uh, why don't you just kill a Chinese kid here?
"怨"有头债有主 我要宰那个...
Not any Chinese kid. That Peking dick
把"吃蛋"视频传到Youtube上的北京小混蛋
who put my tea bag humiliation video on YouTube.
那就这么定了 反正我不在乎奖品
You got a deal. I don't care about the prize.
- 我只想打败Ethel - 咱要做的事儿还多着呢
- I just want to beat Ethel. - We have got a lot of work to do.
这是不争的事实啊
There is no getting around the fact
你的火辣程度也就到年轻时代的John Goodman
that you're about as hot as a young John Goodman.
美国男演员
谢谢表扬
Thank you.
但搞定问答环节和才艺展示 那你肯定能赢
But you can take the whole thing if you nail the Q&A and talent competitions.
我最擅长这两样
Those two are my specialties.
我又可以当选美皇后了
I'll be a pageant queen again.
好哎 先庆祝一下
Yay! Time to celebrate!
马上就会有圣诞节的味儿了
It's beginning to smell a lot like Christmas.
体脂常见问题部位
唇部除须膏
第22届国家公园小姐选美大赛
姑娘们 这比赛我办了22年了
Ladies, I've produced this pageant for 22 years.
记住 你们只要露肉就好
Remember, you're all just sides of beef.
微笑 大家 面带微笑
Smiles, everyone. Smiles.
你没机会的 玩儿去吧你
You don't have a chance. You're... going... down.
等我赢了 玩大提顿这妹子给你看
Yeah, on miss Grand Tetons after I win.
美国大提顿国家公园
够了 Connie 别让她干扰到你 你才是最亮的星
That's it, Connie. Don't let her get in your head. You're a star.
是啊 看见她的人都被亮瞎了
Yeah, 'cause people go blind when they stare at her.
这梗真烂
That sucks.
Malloy 你这些挫笑话还是留着给Aziz Ansari用吧
Malloy, save these crappy jokes for Aziz Ansari.
美国谐星
今晚选美赛的裁判有...
And tonight's pageant will be judged by...
第22届国家公园小姐选美赛
前NBA明星 37个娃儿的爹
former NBA star and father of 37...
外号"雨人" 曾效力于西雅图超音速队
肖恩·坎普
Shawn Kemp!
脱衣舞店老板Jorge
Titty bar owner Jorge!
以及过气演员 苏珊·萨兰登
And washed-up actress Susan Sarandon.
美国女演员 活跃于上世纪七八十年代
现在 有请选手们登场
And now, let's meet our contestants!
这下你怀上我的娃了
Oh, you pregnant now.
这个X代表我 另一个代表你
Now, this "X" is me... this "X" is you...
Tammy就是这个O
and Tammy's the "O."
规则一... 两个X绝对不能碰到
Rule number one... the Xs can never touch.
我有问题 她的洞洞怎么才能大到足够塞进两根"香肠"?
Question. How does her vagina get big enough to fit both of our wieners?
Steve 你个傻X
Steve, you dumbass!
咱俩不会同时在同一个洞里的
We don't go in the same hole at the same time.
严格按规则来
Stick to the game plan.
不许发声 不许玩花样
No audibles. No changing the play.
那我啥时能说点淫荡的? 妹子们就喜欢这个
When can I talk dirty? Girls love this one...
你的阴道看起来额外地湿润
Your vagina looks extra moist.
Steve
Steve!
接下来上场的是Ethel Anderson
Next up, we have Ethel Anderson.
Ethel身高1米7 重43公斤
Ethel is five-foot-six and weighs 95 pounds.
她喜欢吃完就吐 个人爱好有:
She loves eating and vomiting, and her hobbies include:
酒后约炮 炮后内疚
Drunken hook-ups, walks of shame,
以及临产堕胎
and late-term abortions.
不好意思 我只是如实写了我知道的事
Sorry, I just wrote down everything I knew about you.
最后上场的是Connie Cunaman
And finally... Connie Cunaman.
Connie有12手高 牙口好
Connie is 12 hands high with good gums
手是测量马的长度单位
而且很明显 我们的秤就是她压坏的
and apparently... has broken our scale.
Connie 你的比基尼底裤呢?
Connie! Where's your bikini bottom?
在的 被"骆驼趾"夹进去了
It's right here. My camel toe's eating it.
指女性内裤太紧 私处看上去就好像是骆驼的脚趾
看见没?
See?
我带了个充气娃娃来练习
I got this love doll to help us practice.
你先上给我看看
Now show me your moves.
什么动静啊? 你屁股还放阴屁啊?
What is that noise? Is your ass queefing?
人家的菊花一放松就会发出声音嘛
My butthole makes sounds when it's relaxed.
给我夹紧了
Clench that bitch!
接下来的 可是既危险又刺激啊
Now what we about to do is a dangerous dance.
我往左 你就往右
When I go left, you go right.
我玩上面 你来下面
When I go up, you go down.
我亲嘴 你舔菊
When I'm in the mouth, you go South.
我走水路 你去旱路 准备好没?
When I go pink, you go stink. Ready?
一... 二...
One... two...
好 比你快
Ah! I won!
Steve 别跟我说你完事了
Steve, don't tell me you nutted.
问Ethel的第一个问题
Our first question for Ethel
来自前NBA明星 37个娃儿的爹 肖恩·坎普
will come from ex-NBA star and father of 37, Shawn Kemp.
- 这对奶子我喜欢 - 这不算是提问吧
- I like them titties. - That's not actually a question.
这对奶子... 窝喜欢?
I like them... titties?
还是不算提问 你只是升了个调嘛
Still not a question. You just went up at the end.
我来提问吧
I'll ask the question.
《末路狂花》大烂片 (苏珊主演的女权片)
Ethel 你觉得今日女性所面临的最迫切的问题是什么?
Ethel, what do you think is the most pressing issue facing young women today?
我提名苏珊的奶子得"耷拉奖"
- 雪莉·桑德伯格曾说... - 谢谢
- I'd like to quote Sheryl Sandberg... - Thank you.
现任Facebook首席运营官
Connie 还是这个问题
Connie, same question.
上帝保佑我军 保佑小狗狗
God bless the troops. And puppies!
Ethel 给老子用心点
Ethel, get your shit together
那个妻管严的坏蛋会杀了我的
or that pussy-whipped gangster's gonna kill me.
雪天使
Snow angel!
螃蟹步
Crab walk!
空翻蝶
Spin cycle!
一杆进洞
Go for the "O!"
埃菲尔铁塔
Eiffel tower!
我觉得我可以了
I think I'm ready.
- 我一招都没弄错过 - 你的确可以
- I didn't mess up once. - You are ready.
在这种地方都能精神集中的话 在哪都没问题的
And if you can keep your focus here, you can do it anywhere.
床垫大甩卖 七五折
♪ 不知何地 ♪
♪ I don't know where ♪
♪ 不知何时 ♪
♪ I don't know when ♪
♪ 但我深知 爱将开始 ♪
♪ but I know something's about to begin ♪
♪ 睁眼看清 用心感应 ♪
♪ look and you'll know ♪
♪ 某天我会 深驻你心 ♪
♪ some day I'll go inside your world ♪
肖恩 我有了 我也是
跟我比啊 你个婊
Beat that, bitch.
下一位 Ethel Anderson
Next up, Ethel Anderson.
赞 冠军收入囊中
Yes! Now it's in the bag.
Connie的蠢脸就该藏在囊里
Where Connie's face belongs.
懂嘛? Malloy 老子现在平步青云
Eh? Malloy, I'm writing all my own shit now!
又错了 Woodrow 哥在改写剧本了
Wrong again, Woodrow. I'm making some changes.
这场选美大赛马上会丑恶百出
This beauty pageant's about to get ugly.
是嘛? 谁死了轮着你做制片人了?
Oh, yeah? Who died and made you producer?
制片人咯
The producer.
清洁工干的
Cleaning lady did it.
就知道她还窝火呢
Yeah, I guess she's still pissed at me
因为我让她打扫马桶... 当时我还在用
'cause I made her clean the toilet... while I was still on it.
嗨 伙计们
Hi, guys.
甭理他 他一紧张就咯咯傻笑
Oh, don't mind him. When he gets nervous he giggles.
别紧张嘛 我们需要的是彻底的放松
Don't be nervous. We just need to loosen up.
反正我只需要鸡... 尾酒
I know I could use a cock... tail.
今晚玩得愉快
To a fun night.
发生什么了? 我们这是在哪?
What happened? Where are we?
我擦嘞 这婊子疯了
Holy shit! This bitch crazy!
- Tammy? - Tammy死了
- Tammy? - Tammy's gone.
我是蛋碎女王 蛋疼情妇
I am Lady Ballcrusher, mistress of pain!
你俩现在是我的奴隶了
You two are now my slaves!
你... 你干嘛要这么做?
Wh-why are you doing this?
统治傻缺男人让我浴火焚身
It turns me on to dominate stupid men.
- 人家才不傻缺咧 - 闭嘴
- I'm not a stupid men. - Shut up!
全都跪下 像平时一样给我人模狗样起来
Now get on your hands and knees and act like the dogs you are!
Steve 她说让咱们人模狗样 没说让你丫闻我菊花
Steve, just 'cause she told us to be dogs don't mean you have to sniff my ass.
她说让我们咋地?
She told us what now?
欢迎各位 欢迎各位 欢迎各位
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
来到国家公园小姐选美大赛总决赛现场
To the final event of the Miss national park beauty pageant!
下笼子
Cue the cage.
钢铁之笼生死决战
A steel cage death match!
最后一名站立的选手将成为...
Last contestant standing will be...
国家公园小姐
Miss national park!
- 搞毛啊 Malloy? - 给我慢着
- What the hell, Malloy? - Wait a minute.
你的妞儿还想对阵那个红毛大脚怪?
Your girl against that orange bigfoot?
我看我还是抄起玻璃棒
Well, I might as well take the glass rod
直接插进你软软小菊菊里算了
and shove it up your fingle-fangle right now!
我的啥?
My what?
卧槽 漏了老婆大人一个电话
Oh, shit. Missed a call from the wife.
她肯定得毛了 我先逃了
She's gonna be pissed. I gotta run.
等等 软软小菊菊是啥啊?
Wait! What's a fingle-fangle?
放武器
Cue the weapons.
让饥饿游戏开始吧
Let the Hunger Games begin!
这才称得上是大赛
Now this is what I call a pageant.
嗷呜 嗷呜 汪 汪
Woof! Woof! Arf! Arf!
- 我们还得这么着多久啊? - 闭嘴 阿黄
- How much longer do we have to do this? - Shut up, Fido!
我应该是阿黄吧
Uh, I thought I was Fido.
该喂你们狗食了 去去就来
Time for your kibble. Be right back.
- 真特么受够了 - 眼光放长远点 Denzel
- Man, I've had enough of this shit. - Eyes on the prize, Denzel.
过不了多久我们就能玩三人同床啦
It shouldn't be long till we have our threesome.
她好好惹火噢
And she is so hot.
- 你们特么什么人? - 我是阿黄 他是火火
- Who the [Bleep] are you? - I'm Fido. He's Sparky.
你们丫是要干我老婆嘛?
Are you two screwing my wife?
- 不然我们干嘛来了 - Steve
- That's why we're here. - Steve!
抱歉 不然汪们干嘛来了汪
Oh, sorry. Rat's rhy re're rere!
- 我宰了你们混账 - 汪呜
- I'll kill you bastards! - Ruh-roh.
你敢宰一个试试
Oh, you're not killing anyone.
发生什么了 Tammy? 你劈腿了嘛?
What's going on, Tammy? Are you cheating on me?
闭嘴 这俩货是来玩三人同床的
Shut up! These guys are here for a threesome.
- 我就必须成全他们 - 赞
- And they're gonna have it! - Yes!
- 你们仨 - 啥啥啥玩意儿?
- With you. - W-W-W-What?
- 我们仨? - 没错
- With me? - Yes.
别磨叽了 给我三人同床玩起来
Now stop delaying and start three-waying.
好哒 小亲亲 为你啥都行
Okay, sweetie. Anything for you.
- 别介 别听她的 - 对不住了 哥们儿
- No! Don't listen to her! - Sorry, guys.
在婚姻里 男人必须直面挑战
In a marriage, you've got to choose your battles.
你屌得过我嘛
Then choose this one!
收到你短信了 Tammy 没啥事吧?
I got your text, Tammy. Everything okay?
- 闭嘴 给我滚过去 - 好的
- Shut up and get in there! - Okay.
其实吧 这还真不是今天我干过最诡异的事儿
You know, this isn't even the weirdest thing I've done today.
这儿是我的决杀场 贱人
This is my octagon, bitch.
我擦
Oh, shit.
- 谁说我赢不了大赛来着? - Connie
- So who can't win a pageant anymore? - Connie!
妈咪 你到这儿干嘛来了?
Mommy? What are you doing here?
我想着看看你在大赛上拼搏 或许会让我再爱上你的
I thought seeing you in a pageant might make me love you again.
然后呢?
And?
就没有然后了
Still not feeling it.
来吧 扣动扳机
Go ahead. Pull the trigger.
谢谢你让我解脱
You'd be doing me a favor.
从没人爱过我 以后也不会有了
Nobody loves me and nobody ever will.
不
No.
你说得对 Connie
You were right, Connie.
选美大赛确实毁一生
Beauty pageants do destroy people's lives.
全都因为我们把胜负看得比天还高
And all because we place winning above everything.
现在 我要说一切结束了
Well, I say that ends now.
今晚 我们是双冠王
Tonight, we are co-champions!
哎好窝心啊 Ethel 不过猜怎么着?
Aw, that's sweet, Ethel. But guess what?
双冠王你个大头鬼啊
There's no such thing as co-champions!
我是国家公园小姐
I'm Miss national park!
- 我完蛋了 - 我要去中国了
- And I'm screwed. - And I'm going to China.
回来之前你葬礼先别办
Don't have your funeral till I get back.
我要成心错过才行
I want to miss it intentionally.
♪ 她诞生了 ♪
♪ There she is! ♪
♪ 国家公园小姐 ♪
♪ Miss national park! ♪
姓常的在家嘛?
Is Chang here?
- 你好呀 姓常的 - Malloy 你怎么来的?
- Hello, Chang. - Malloy. How you get here?
坐灰机来的 但这不是重点
I took a "prane." But that doesn't matter.
plane发音为prane意在吐槽亚洲口音
我来是要亲手灭了你的
I am here to destroy you in person.
我的天呐 我不知道...
Oh, my God. I had no idea...
这事儿这么容易
it was gonna be this easy.
Roger & Waco: 本片两位创作者的名字
你确定要这么干?
You sure about this?
我觉得那种三人同床也没那么糟嘛
I didn't think that threesome went that bad.
闭你丫的嘴吧 Steve 年轻人的下三路麻烦太多
Oh, shut the hell up, Steve. Young pussy's too much trouble.
把我敲回那个爱老女人的过去
Knock me back into liking old bitches.
好的吧 兄弟 你愿意就行呀
Okay, buddy. If that's what you want.
打扰下 好孩子 我们想问点事情
Excuse me, Sonny. We need some help.
- 哎唷 瞧瞧这小骚逼 - 说你自己呢嘛
- Well, hello there, sexy. - Hello, yourself.
没搭理你
I wasn't talking to you.
哥说的是下边这朵惹火小雏菊
I was talking to that hot piece of ass right there.
糟糕 用力过猛了我
Oops. I think I hit him too hard.
你们这是什么公园?
What kind of park is this?
咋了 McGill? 你咋这么心不在焉?
What's wrong, McGill? You just don't seem into it.
跟老婆大人闹了点儿别扭
Just a little trouble with the wife.
说起来我不是什么理疗师哈 不过...
Well, I'm not a licensed therapist, but...
过去我有一招儿对付我老婆特管用
there's something that's worked with my wives in the past.
安息吧 Tammy
- 扯平了? - 扯平了
- Even? - Even.
欢迎微博关注@漫迪字幕组
weibo.com/weheartcartoons